gourmetsleuth.com 2019-10-23

# Privacy Policy - Gourmetsleuth

  * ###  Privacy & Cookies 

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, note that some parts of the gourmetsleuth.com™ web site and its functionality and links will not function properly or may be considerably slower if you refuse cookies. For example, without cookies, you may have difficulty completing shopping transactions, entering giveaways, or creating your personal profile. You can order your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered. Then you can decide whether to accept one or not. If you want to control which cookies your computer accepts, just follow the instructions for your particular Internet browser system located at http://www.microsoft.com/info/privacy.htm. 

  * ###  Email Addresses 

E-mail addresses and other personally identifying data about you is known to gourmetsleuth.com™ only when you voluntarily submit or post it to gourmetsleuth.com™. We collect your e-mail addresses only if you post a message to us, if you communicate with us via e-mail, or if you volunteer it for any reason, such as survey information and/or site registration. We do not share this information with any other source or company.

  * ###  Disclaimer. 

The Privacy Policy adopted by gourmetsleuth.com and all statements contained on this site about privacy and how we deal with data supplied by visitors to this site are not intended to be a contractual obligation of any kind and any such obligation is hereby disclaimed. These statements constitute the present policy of gourmetsleuth.com™ as to which it will take reasonable measures to implement. Similarly this Privacy Policy is not intended to be "advertising" or "advertising claims." Rather it is intended to set forth our policy, including our practices and intentions about how we conduct our business 

  * ###  3rd Party Advertisers 

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information ( _e.g.,_ the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out system). 

  * ###  Correction of Your Personal Profile 

You can always edit any personal information you give gourmetsleuth.com™ by editing your profile screen which is located here.

My Profile at GourmetSleuth.com \- Use this link for editing information regarding your site activities, like contributing recipes, comments or websites.

There will always be a link to manage your email preferences provided at the bottom of any newsletter or update from GourmetSleuth.

  * ###  Opt-Out of Future Communications. 

You will only be contacted by us for order confirmations or order related communications OR if you have subscribed to any of our newsletters either on our main Gourmetsleuth.com site or our store located at Store.Gourmetsleuth.com.  If for any reason you no longer wish to receive communications from gourmetsleuth.com™ please email such request to us or check off an opt-out box provided for that purpose as it appears on any newsletter or update communication. 

  * ###  Other Personal Information 

We do not collect or preserve any information about you other than that information you provide to us when you fill in our membership form. That information is not shared with any other source or company.   

  * ###  Affiliate Links 

Some of our pages throughout our site contain links to affiliates, primarily Amazon.com. When a user clicks on one of those links and makes a purchase we may receive a small fee from that affiliate. This is not the case with all of our links. We link to many sites that sell products or provide services just because we have found them to be good, reliable sources for information and not because we receive any type of compensation.  We are an Amazon affiliate and some of those links to Amazon may result in a small fee to us if you make a purchase. 

## Product Reviews

On occasion, we are provided reviews for products which have been given to us to test or sample. We provide factual information about the product and it is not swayed by the fact the product was received for free. Any review about a product that was provided to us at no charge will contain a statement disclosing that information.

  * ###  Reviews 

Gourmetsleuth occasionally receives products for review at no charge and we also purchase products for review.  When products are provided to us we provide a non-biased, honest review.  The review will state if we received the product at no charge. 

## Our Privacy Policy & Terms Of Use

**PLEASE READ CAREFULLY. BY USING THIS SITE, YOU SIGNIFY YOUR ACCEPTANCE TO THESE TERMS OF USE.** If you do not agree with any of the below Terms of Use, do not use this site. 

Gourmetsleuth.com™ reserves the right, at any time, to modify, alter, or update these Terms of Use, and you agree to be bound by such modifications, alterations, or updates.materials you see on this web site and your use of them.
